import 'package:flutter/material.dart';
import 'package:qs_app/components/mcqs_content_box.dart';

class EteaGeneralscienceContentScreen extends StatelessWidget {
  @override
  Widget build(BuildContext context) {
    return Scaffold(
      appBar: AppBar(
        title: Text('ETEA General Science'),
      ),
      body: SingleChildScrollView(
        child: Padding(
          padding: EdgeInsets.all(20.0),
          child: Column(
            children: [

              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Which Asian city will host the commonwealth games in 2010?',
                option1: 'Islamabad',
                option2: 'Tokyo',
                option3: 'Colombo',
                option4: 'New Delhi',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Durand Cup is associated with the games of?',
                option1: 'Cricket',
                option2: 'Volleyball',
                option3: 'Hockey',
                option4: 'Football',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Which of the following is the term for a sumo wrestling tournament?',
                option1: 'Dogan',
                option2: 'Eisai',
                option3: 'Basho',
                option4: 'Bento',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'What was the very first official badminton club?',
                option1: 'The badminton health club',
                option2: 'The bad Ass badminton club',
                option3: 'The IBF badminton club',
                option4: 'The bath badminton club',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),

              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Each Summer Olympics has its own motto. What is the motto of the 2012 games?',
                option1: 'One World, one dream',
                option2: 'Inspire a generation',
                option3: 'The celebration of the country',
                option4: 'Dare to dream',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'The term Butterfly is associated with?',
                option1: 'Boxing',
                option2: 'Wrestling',
                option3: 'Kabaddi',
                option4: 'Swimming',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'In which year did pate Sampras win his first Grand Slam singles title?',
                option1: '1989',
                option2: '1991',
                option3: '1990',
                option4: '1993',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'The ninth cricket world cup was played in 2007, won by?',
                option1: 'Sri Lanka',
                option2: 'Pakistan',
                option3: 'India',
                option4: 'Irland',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'e',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'What country is the birthplace of Steffi Graf?',
                option1: 'Germany',
                option2: 'Austria',
                option3: 'Belgium',
                option4: 'Sweden',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'The 2005 Australian Open Tennis Championship titles for men’s and women’s singles were won, respectively by?',
                option1: 'Pete Sampras and Steffi Graf',
                option2: 'Rafael Nadal and Venus Williams',
                option3: 'Marat Safin and Serena Williams',
                option4: 'Andre Agassi and Arantxa Sanchez-Vicario',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'The term Tee is connected with?',
                option1: 'Golf',
                option2: 'Polo',
                option3: 'Billiards',
                option4: 'Bridge',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Which of the following pieces of safely equipment would be almost mandatory to play squash?',
                option1: 'Knee pads',
                option2: 'Eye Goggles',
                option3: 'Helmet',
                option4: 'Elbow pads',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'I defeated my little sister to win the 2008 Wimbledon championships trophy.Who am i?',
                option1: 'Serena Williams',
                option2: 'Rafael Nadal',
                option3: 'Vanessa Williams',
                option4: 'Venus Williams',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Who won the first world cup competition?',
                option1: 'Sri Lanka',
                option2: 'West Indies',
                option3: 'East Africa',
                option4: 'Pakistan',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'If 4-a>5, then?',
                option1: 'a < -1',
                option2: 'a > -1',
                option3: 'a > 1',
                option4: 'a < 1',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Who was the first sumo wrestler to weigh in at more than 600 pounds (272.7 Kg)?',
                option1: 'Kasugao',
                option2: 'Akebono',
                option3: 'Musashimaru',
                option4: 'Konishiki',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'The ninth cricket world cup was played in 2011, won by?',
                option1: 'England',
                option2: 'Australia',
                option3: 'West Indies',
                option4: 'India',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'In Japan what is Kyudo the name for?',
                option1: 'A martial art form',
                option2: 'A traditional form of archery',
                option3: 'A mode of wrestling',
                option4: 'A form of football',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Lance Armstrong a sportsperson of international repute, belongs to which of the following countries?',
                option1: 'Spain',
                option2: 'USA',
                option3: 'Brazil',
                option4: 'Ukraine',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'The Olympic motto was first displayed on the Olympics Flag in the games held in?',
                option1: '2000',
                option2: '1972',
                option3: '1920',
                option4: '1894',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'World’s fastest sportsman Usain blot belongs to which Country?',
                option1: 'Jamaica',
                option2: 'South Africa',
                option3: 'USA',
                option4: 'Kenya',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'What is number of Nations participated in London Olympics 2012?',
                option1: '207',
                option2: '206',
                option3: '208',
                option4: '204',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Who started the ancient Olympic games?',
                option1: 'The Egyptians',
                option2: 'The Jews',
                option3: 'The Romans',
                option4: 'The Greeks',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Find the missing numbers. 7 10 9 12 11 —– —–?',
                option1: '14 and 13',
                option2: '13 and 16',
                option3: '15 and 13',
                option4: '17 and 13',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Insert the word that means the same as the words outside the brackets. Shape (. . . .) Class?',
                option1: 'Rubber',
                option2: 'Form',
                option3: 'Pine',
                option4: 'Iron',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Insert the missing letter. R T P R N P?',
                option1: 'M',
                option2: 'N',
                option3: 'L',
                option4: 'O',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'C',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Insert the word that means the same as the words outside the brackets. Flame (. . . .) Shoot?',
                option1: 'Site',
                option2: 'Fire',
                option3: 'Fox',
                option4: 'Lame',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Insert the word that means the same as the words outside the brackets. Friend (. . . ) Join?',
                option1: 'Mate',
                option2: 'Mine',
                option3: 'Made',
                option4: 'Mile',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Insert the missing number. 8 5 2 4 2 0 9 6?',
                option1: '2',
                option2: '3',
                option3: '4',
                option4: '1',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Insert the missing word. Quips (punt) Stern Quote (. . . ) Begin?',
                option1: 'Tin',
                option2: 'Tone',
                option3: 'Tipe',
                option4: 'Tune',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
            ],
          ),
        ),
      ),
    );
  }
}


